Mighty Little Defenders 4 – Ultimate Battle: The Next Generation.
A Mysterious Rock Appears
Episode 1
When Big Humphrey told us the news, I was so startled.
Green Green Grassland will become a high-tech city after all.
I’m going to miss the Green Green Grassland we have now.
No need to be sad about it.
We’re making a time capsule to commemorate it, after all.
Just keep digging!
You need to help out, too.
Alright, the hole is ready.
Next up will be…
The time capsule is ready, too.
I’m putting a dumbbell inside.
I’m putting in a letter to my future self.
I’ll just put a few snacks in there, then.
Paddi, those few snacks won’t fit in there.
I guess I’ll just eat them now, then.
Big brothers and sisters…
We want to put a picture book into the time capsule.
Wolffy, I thought you’d put one of your inventions in there.
Well, that’s because Wilie drew this.
It depicts our past adventures.
It’s something more important than inventions.
Daddy, I want to go on more adventures with you in the future.
No problem, son.
Let’s close the capsule, then.
Wait.
There’s one more thing I want to put in.
Time to eat.
The last one misses out.
Am I that heavy?
It wasn’t your fault, Paddi.
There’s so much smoke.
Let’s go take a look.
Whatever it was crashed up right ahead.
This is…
What a big crater!
Let’s just keep looking.
Everyone, be careful.
There’s something over…
Was this crater caused by that strange stone?
If I’m not mistaken…
This…this season, I finally get to be the main character!
Sparky!
Thunder Summon!
Invent my creation!
Why isn’t there any reaction?
In that case, how about we take the stone to Mr. Slowy?
Right!
Once Mr. Slowy solves the mystery of the stone, I can become the main character!
Wait for us…
Why can’t I seem to get any results?
Mr. Slowy, we’ve made a huge discovery.
We just picked up this strange rock.
What?
What was that just now…
It’s not reacting anymore…
Looks like I really need to study this properly.
After studying it for so long…
All I know now is that this rock holds immense energy,
and that there’s some kind of connection between the rock and the robot.
But our current technology still can’t decipher it.
I need to study it some more.
What are you all still doing here?
The celebration is about to start, yet here you are.
We almost forgot—let’s go!
We’ll let the computer continue analyzing, then.
It’s so lively.
Today marks the celebration of Green Green Grassland’s
transformation into a high-technology city.
Science and technology constitute the primary productive force.
Green Green Grassland is sure to have a bright future.
Great!
To mark this fresh start, let’s all take a group photo.
Positions, everyone.
Let’s all grab a bite to eat while we wait for the fireworks display.
A technology city, huh?
I’m really looking forward to it.
What will Green Green Grassland be like in the future?
And what will we be like?
I…I’ll definitely be taller than Daddy.
I’m happy just being with everyone here.
I’m going to keep guarding Goats’ Village and protect everyone.
I guess I’ll just eat even more.
You really haven’t changed a bit.
What about you, Weslie?
As for me, I’m going to…
Wolffy.
They want to have a barbecue, but they forgot to bring the grill.
So…let’s go to the lab and get it together.
Okay, let’s go.
Daddy, I want to go, too.
Be a good kid; have an tangerine while you wait for Daddy.
Daddy will be right back after you finish it.
Daddy…
Let’s go, Wolffy.
Wait for Daddy, alright?
♪ Even though I’m just a little goat (wolf)… ♪
How is the door open already?
How about we take a look?
Who are you?
Is that strange stone yours?
You still haven’t answered my question.
Who exactly are you?
I’ll catch you, Weslie.
Oh no!
What kind of weapon is this?
It can actually turn things into iron.
A portal?
We can’t let him take that stone.
Let’s go after him!
What is this place?
Look!
If we keep hesitating,
he’s going to get away.
After him!
I’m not a very good swimmer.
Watch out!
Are you okay, Weslie?
I’m fine.
He’s about to get away.
Weslie, let’s fly over there.
Don’t forget me!
Don’t even think about it.
Stop right there.
Haven’t Weslie and Wolffy come back yet?
Yeah.
I’m practically starving.
It’s so beautiful!
It really is beautiful!
It’s a real shame Weslie and Wolffy can’t see this.
Daddy…
Stop right there.
End